ILGWU. Wilbur Daniels papers, 5780/084
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. General/Administrative, 1937-1985
  - Sol C. Chaikin. President; Secretary-Treasurer, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Memo re Democratic Agenda; correspondence with Ray Rogers - Corporate Campaign Director ACTWU; with New York Governor Carey; re International Rescue Committee; "Labor's Man to Watch" by A.H. Raskin - on Chaikin; correspondence with Secretary of Labor Ray Marshall; "The Impact of Exports on American Economy" by Sol C. Chaikin; routine
  - Sol C. Chaikin. Dinner, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    guest lists; RSVP's; invitations; routine
  - Charities, 1966-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Correspondence with Citizens Housing and Planning Council; Parson's School of Design; MET; National Labor Council - City of Hope; Xerox; The Equitable Life Assurance Society of US; Transition House; Educational Foundation for Fashion Industries; Manhattan School of Music; National Trade Union for Human Rights; routine
  - Coalition For Rural America, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    "The Economic and Social Condition of Rural America in the 1970's" - Committee on Governmental Operations; Release - "Senator James Pearson Points to Need for Rural Political Action"; Remarks of Senator Hubert H. Humphrey before Coalition For Rural America Board Meeting; Preliminary Draft of a Prospectus Outlining the Goals and Objectives of the Coalition for Rural America; list of persons invited to serve on Board of Directors; Center for Balanced National Growth - Board Meeting Minutes; memo from Coalition For Rural America re Senate Version of Rural Development Act of 1972; routine
  - Cohen, Martin S., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Statement of Case: Antonio Maltese v. David Dubinsky (President of ILWGU)
  - Committee of 400, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Report to G.E.B.; correspondence to Louis Stulberg from Local 99; correspondence re Committee of 400; transcript re telephone call to Hermione Hart from Committee of 400; correspondence re Investigation of Committee of 400; Report from International Security Bureau re Committee of 400; routine
  - Committee on Stulberg Hospital (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Undated. List of committee
  - Computer Consultants, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Correspondence with Compusize, Inc.; "Role of the Computer in Knitted Apparel" by W.H. Bartley; memo re New Machines and New Procedures; "Negotiating and Contracting for Computers and EDP Support Services"; correspondence with International Microfilmers; memo re Computerized Operations; Leader Data Processing Company; routine
  - Constitution of ILGWU [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Memos re ILGWU Constitution; Dues Rate Analysis; Minutes of Constitution Revision Committee; Press Release re 33rd Convention of ILGWU; ILGWU Constitution; "Coalition Against Dishwasher"; memo re 1977 Constitution; "Electing Union Officers"; routine
  - Constitution of ILGWU [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Consumer Price Index, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Percentage Changes in Consumer Price Index
  - Consumers, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    "Your Money's Worth" by Sidney Margolius; memo from Sarah Newman of Consumer Clearing House re United National Consumers Association; correspondence re Department of Transportation; routine
  - Cost of Living, 1965-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Annual Price Survey - Family Budget Costs; Escalator Clause - National Dress Makers Association, Inc. 1967-70; Cost of Living Requests; memo re DJC Agreement and cost of living changes; memo from Lazar Teper re Use of Consumer Price Index under ILGWU agreements; memos and correspondence re cost of living increases; Changes in Consumer Price Index; Application of ILGWU For Decontrol of Wages in Women's Garment Industry to cost of Living Council; correspondence with Cost of Living Council; routine
  - Death Benefit Department, 1968-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Death Benefit Fund Rules and Regulations - 1965, 1971; Report 1965-67 Death Benefit Fund, 1968; correspondence re withdrawal covered by ILGWU Death Benefit Fund; memos re proposed Death Benefit Fund Changes; Reports from Death Benefit Department; Basic Facts about ILGWU Death Benefit Fund; Proposed Amendments
  - Deluxe Fashions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Summary Schedules; audit; routine
  - Directives [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1967 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    ILGWU Investigation Policy; correspondence to all ILGWU Organizations and all Welfare and Retirement Funds; correspondence with regional, department and area directors; Report of Personnel Review Committee; correspondence re withdrawal covered by ILGWU Death Benefit Fund; correspondence to all ILGWU organizations; correspondence re all Health and Welfare Funds; Special Assistance Fund; dues exemption during military service; damage for use of non-ILGWU contractors; Master Agreement with Local 153, OPEIU; re Liability Insurance Coverage; routine
  - Directives [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Directives, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Memo re increased maximum weekly Disability Benefits; Union Health Center; Personnel Review Committee decisions; agreement provision on production of accessories; right to strike; labor disputes and struck work; routine
  - Directives [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Correspondence re Special Benefit for Experimental Drugs; Master Public Liability Insurance; Personnel Review Committee decisions; Pooled Donations Fund; policy on non-assessables; Convention Call; Agreement with Local 153 OPEIU; correspondence re 60-day and 30-day Notices for Contract Termination; Master Agreements Department; routine
  - Directives [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Directives, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Correspondence re Personnel Review Committee decision; union label; Survival of the Contract upon Sale of Shop; endorsement of McGovern-Shriver; Import Demonstration; EEO-3; routine
  - Directives [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Memo re ILGWU Investment Policy; correspondence re Social Security Taxes on Health and Welfare Fund Benefits; Personnel Review Committee decision; Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund; Social Security Taxes on vacation benefits; Single vs. Multi-Plant Bargaining; FICA Taxes on vacation benefits; routine
  - Directives [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Directives, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Correspondence re Personnel Review Committee decision; 1974 Convention; revision of Learner Regulations under $2 Minimum Wage; routine
  - Directives, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re Personnel Review Committee Decision; leave in case of death in family; Health and Welfare Benefits; Union Label TV Commercials; Pooled Donations Fund; routine
  - Disability Benefits, 1950-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Procedure in Connection with Disability Benefits for Employees of ILGWU Affiliates of New York State; memo re ILGWU Sick Benefit Plan; Pregnancy Disability Benefit Claim; Illness Benefits and Disability; routine
  - Dubinsky, David, 1966-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Correspondence with International Rescue Committee; AFL-CIO Executive Council Statement on Benefit Plan legislation; correspondence re Datatron v. Dubinsky; Proposal to the Dubinsky Foundation to finance the Third Annual Conference of A. Phillip Randolph Institute Affiliates; correspondence re 1972 David Dubinsky Foundation Awards; newspaper clippings; routine
  - Dues Summary ILGWU, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    General Motors Corporate-Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity Law; memo re Civil Rights Investigation; ILGWU National Retirement Fund memos re EEOC Guidelines on Discrimination in Pension Plans Because of Sex; memo from Emil Schlesinger re Racial Discrimination; OFCCP -Practice and Procedures; EEOC - Practices and Procedures; EEOC Finding Determination; routine
  - Fair Labor Standards Act [folder 1 of 2], 1937-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Trade Practice Rules for the Covered Button and Buckle Manufacturing Industry; Trade Practice Rules for the Popular Priced Dress Manufacturing Industry; Trade Practice Rules for the Cotton Converting Industry; Statement to the Fair Labor Standards Board by Wilbur Daniels re Wage Minimums; Working Draft Proposal of Fair Labor Standards Act Amendment; correspondence with Senator Harrison Williams, Jr. re Fair Labor Standards Act Amendment; Statement to Fair Labor Standards Act Amendment by Mary Keyserling; routine
  - Fair Labor Standards Act [folder 2 of 2], 1937-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Federal Election Campaign Act (FECA) [folder 1 of 4], 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    "Federal Register" - Federal Communications Commission; Federal Election Campaign Act of 1971; Public Law 92-225 Appendix - Federal Election Campaign Act; memo from James Lipsig re FECA of 1971; Interstate Commerce and Political Campaigns - ICC Proposals to Prohibit Extension of Credit without Security; "Federal Register" - Federal Communications Commission - Comptroller General; Citizen's Research Foundation - "Federal Regulation of Campaign Finance: Some Constitutional Questions"; correspondence re Campaign Committee; newspaper clippings; Supreme Court Decision: Pipefitters Local 1562; Frontlash Organizing News; US House of Representatives - Report of Receipts and Expenditures of ILGWU Campaign Committee; routine
  - Federal Election Campaign Act (FECA) [folder 2 of 4], 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Federal Election Campaign Act (FECA) [folder 3 of 4], 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Federal Election Campaign Act (FECA) [folder 4 of 4], 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    memo re FTC and labeling of goods made of textiles processed into garments abroad and thereafter imported to US; FTC News Releases; memo re customs requirements on labeling; routine
  - Financial Information, 1965-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Summary Statements; correspondence re dues; Reports submitted to Finance Department; Receipts; memos re Amalgamated Houses correspondence re Proposed Amalgamated Housing Loan; routine
  - Financial Reports. Union and Non-Union, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    NCO - Specialized Credit Reports re Vanity Brassiere Company; Canadian Lady; Top Mode Manufacturing Company; Hem House, Inc.; Adorence Company, Inc.; Judy Bond, Inc.; routine
  - General Office Statement of Income and Expense, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Correspondence with Green Dolmatch; newspaper ads and clippings; ILGWU - Advertising Program and Schedule 1976-77; Radio Schedules and Spot Rotations; ILGWU Radio Spot Campaign; Indemnity Agreements - John Glucksman of Green Dolmatch; estimates; song words; correspondence re ads and song; Delegates Guide to 36th ILGWU Convention; tapes; routine
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 2 of 3], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 3 of 3], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Correspondence with Green Dolmatch; RHR Filmedia - folder; correspondence with Heidepriem/Santandrea Inc. re ads; with Congressional House staff; newspaper clippings; The Gallagher Report - "Crackdown Coming on Advocacy Advertising"; correspondence with Robert E. O'Donnell and Associates, Inc.; Network Television Audience analysis; routine
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Green Dolmatch Advertising [folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Green Dolmatch. Radio/TV Stations [folder 1 of 3], 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Correspondence with Green Dolmatch; New York City Radio Spot Campaign; correspondence with Swedish Broadcasting Corporation; ILGWU Advertising Program and Schedule 1976-77; correspondence re Puerto Rico advertising; Bette Midler special sponsorship; ILGWU General Labor Council Promotion Fund statement/summary; ad copies; Advertising Budget Summary
  - Green Dolmatch. Radio/TV Stations [folder 2 of 3], 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Green Dolmatch. Radio/TV Stations [folder 3 of 3], 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Group Health Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Group Health Inc. - Board Meeting; correspondence with Group Health Insurance
  - Hampton, Eugene Local 203, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re death benefits; trust fund/indenture for children; trust Fund For Children of Eugene Hampton; correspondence re naming local after Hampton
  - Health and Welfare Funds, 1966-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Memo re Program Planning for Health Care from Columbia University; Summary Statements; Medicare Cost Estimates; 1967 Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplementary Unemployment Funds; Report of Health and Welfare Department to G.E.B.; memo re Tax Withholding on ILGWU Health Benefits; Bylaws, Rules, and Regulations of Health and Welfare Fund; "Health and Welfare Benefits Program"; Joint and Survivor Option - Staff Retirement Fund; routine
  - Health and Welfare Fund. Delinquencies, Annual Report [folder 1 of 2], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Summary of Audit Report; correspondence re collection of sums due Welfare fund; memo re benefit fund charges and collections; Summary - Master Agreement Department Schedule of Liquidated Damages Collections For Non-Affiliated Contractors; Summary of Balances Dues; routine
  - Health and Welfare Fund. Delinquencies, Annual Report [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Health and Welfare Funds. Taxation, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Correspondence re IRS; statement of Edwin S. Cohen, Assistant Secretary of the Treasury for Tax Policy; memo re Present Status of Various Tax Matters Relating to Collectively Bargained Health and Welfare Funds; routine
  - Health Services Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9a)
    1967 Report of Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplementary Unemployment Funds; memo re Vice President Bambace's report to G.E.B.; Proposed Drug Plan; memos re drug program; Agenda of Worker's Benefits Committee; memo re Modification Agreement - Health Services Plan; MediData Management Systems - pamphlet/cost estimate; Bylaws, Rules, and Regulations of ILGWU Health Services Plan; Modifications; Minutes of Health Services Board; Tax Reform Act Resolution; Meeting of Executive Committee - Minutes; Trust Indenture Creating the ILGWU Health Services Plan; S.U.B. Benefits - Comparison between Present and Proposed Plans; routine
  - Health Services Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9b)
  - Highlander Ltd. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Undated. Specialized Credit Reports; newspaper clippings
  - Hoffmann, Kim. Interior Decorator, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Correspondence with Kim Hoffmann re working agreement; estimates; blueprints; routine
  - Holiday Pay, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Memo from New York State Department of Labor Division of Employment re Special Bulletin Benefits Claims during Vacation Periods and Holidays; memo re Holiday Pay and Unemployment Insurance in New York, Connecticut, and New Jersey
  - Hopi Tribe, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Business Lease of Hopi Tribe to Western Superior Corporation; memo re Hopi Tribe and the BVD Company, Inc.
  - Humphrey, Hubert folder 1 of 2], 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Invitations; correspondence re Apparel Industries Committee for Humphrey; correspondence with Committee of Arts and Letters for Humphrey; re National Gala for Humphrey; guest lists; "Humphrey, The Vital Center" by Gus Tyler
  - Humphrey, Hubert folder 2 of 2], 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Washington Report - Senator Hubert Humphrey; Address Contribution Lists; contribution Receipts; correspondence Gala Committee for Humphrey; Receipt Summary Sheets; routine
  - Immigration Project, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Report Project
  - Imports [folder 1 of 5], 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    "Legislative Campaign for a Federal Minimum Wage (1955)" by Gus Tyler; Resolution on Imports - Adopted by G.E.B. 1966; Press Release re Cabinet Committee Sets Import Goal; Partial List of US Manufacturers that Import Garments From Abroad; Fact Sheet on Imports; newspaper clippings; memo re Textile Meeting with President Nixon; "Why Exports Are Becoming Irrelevant"; correspondence re Imports; Comments on Foreign Trade and Investment Act of 1972 - Quantitative Restraints on Imports by Lazar Teper; Public Relations Projects - ILGWU Import Program Reports; Preliminary Proposals for ILGWU Campaign on Foreign Merchandise; memos re anti- import program; Analysis of Tax Provisions; Memorandum of Understanding; Digest of Agreement with Hong Kong, Japan; "Union Label Means Human Living Standards"; The White House - Position Strategy for Import Problem; "Crisis - Imports vs. Jobs"; Steelworkers Legislative Newsletter - Trade Adjustment Assistance; Minutes of Textile/Apparel Import Steering Group; Statement by Wilbur Daniels before Informal Textile Committee; Multilateral Trade Negotiations News - Progress Made Toward MTN Conclusions; Textile Agreements Negotiated under Multifiber Arrangement; ILGWU Import Program by Rothstein, Matheson, Arrington; routine
  - Imports [folder 2 of 5], 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Imports [folder 3 of 5], 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Imports [folder 4 of 5], 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Imports [folder 5 of 5], 1955-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Industrial Development and Job Opportunities. Seminar (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Undated. Guest List; change in non-agricultural and manufacturing employment
  - Industrial Union Department (IUD), 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Correspondence re Industrial Union Department Convention; IUD - Convention Call Seventh Constitutional Convention; memo re NLRB Election History Information for 1966; IUD Contract Summary Form; IUD - Certified Audit for 1969; Resolution - Grape Strikers' Victory; Resolution - OSH; Convention Call - Ninth; memo re IUD Conference on Trade; routine
  - Institute For The Study of the Holocaust, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Correspondence with Moshe Dector, Director; Prospectus
  - Insurance, 1956-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Memo re Insurance Program; Master Insurance Schedule; correspondence re Workmen's Compensation Placement; routine
  - Internal Revenue Investigation re Health and Welfare Fund, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Summary of IRS Examination; correspondence re IRS investigation; routine
  - Interstate Taxation, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Statement in Behalf of the Apparel Industry by Sidney S. Korzenik re H.R. 11798 (Bill to Regulate and Foster Commerce Among States by providing a system for taxation of Interstate Commerce); Summary of Proposed Interstate Taxation Act; Bill; routine
  - Investments, 1965-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Securities and Exchange Commission - Form N-IR - for annual report of registered management investment company; routine
  - Japan, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Current Japanese Wages and Trends; Japanese Wages and Labor Market; correspondence with Richard Sneider - Minister at American Embassy; newspaper clippings; Information re Japan Zensen Domei (Textile Workers) team; routine
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Apparel Industries Committee to Elect Lyndon B. Johnson. [folder 1 of 5], 1964- 1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    "Political Contributions by Corporations in Federal Elections" by H. Barrow Farr, Jr.; General Resolution of Unincorporated Association; List of Pledges made; List - Checks Received For Liberal Digest; Contribution Lists; Lists - Checks Received for Apparel Industry For Johnson; List of Checks Received and Deposited; List of Checks Received and Deposited - Luncheon Account; correspondence with House of Representatives; routine
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Apparel Industries Committee to Elect Lyndon B. Johnson. [folder 2 of 5], 1964- 1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Apparel Industries Committee to Elect Lyndon B. Johnson. [folder 3 of 5], 1964- 1965 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Apparel Industries Committee to Elect Lyndon B. Johnson. [folder 4 of 5], 1964- 1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Apparel Industries Committee to Elect Lyndon B. Johnson. [folder 5 of 5], 1964- 1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Justice (Official Publication) Leon Stein, Editor, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Newspaper clippings and translation re "AFL-CIO will leave Puerto Rico" Nosotros; "NAACP Charges AFL-CIO with Discrimination"; correspondence re Justice Mailing; routine
  - Labels, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Correspondence re labels and prices; labels for master agreement firms; Procedure for handling Union Labels; Union Label Rules and Regulations; Labels; routine
  - Learner Bulletins (Research Department), 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Regional Distribution of Employment in Women's and Children's Wear Industries 1974, 1958, 1962, 1963; Learner Exemptions Granted by Wage and Hour Division
  - Legal Aid Society [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Minutes of Campaign Planning Committee; correspondence re Legal Aid Society Theatre Party 1965-70; Theatre Arrangements; routine
  - Legal Aid Society [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Legal Aid Society [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Legal Department, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Petition for Review of Wage Order of Secretary of Labor; correspondence re Miranda vs. Associated Medical Facilities, Inc.; memo re President's Report to G.E.B.; Labor Relations Bulletin - Right of Strikers To Return To Their Jobs; memo re staff mortgages; correspondence re Committee on Equal Opportunity Law; Labor Relations Bulletin - Cutter's or Cutting Department Bargaining Unit; memo re Vacation Clauses in Master Agreements; routine
  - Legal Department, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Memo re Summary of Events Leading to Closing of Dunkirk Lingerie, Inc.; correspondence with Max Zimny, Associate General Counsel; Tax Reform Law; Mansco International Corporation; Sick Benefit Plan; routine
  - Legal Department, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    American Bar Association - Special Committee on Prepaid Legal Insurance; memo re Lawsuit of Datatron, Inc. (formerly Mailers, Inc.) v. International; Federal Tax on Union Health and Welfare Funds; "Tax Status of Labor Unions and Related Organizations"; memo re Commission on Bankruptcy Laws
  - Legal Department, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Correspondence re Morris Glushien, General Counsel, dinner; memo re Survival of Contract upon Sale of Shop; Report of Legal Department to G.E.B. 1979 - Recent Legal Developments; "The Union and Its Members: Rights and Responsibilities"; routine
  - Legal Services. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Undated. Court of Appeals of New York: Norma Crowe v. Dates Laundry Service, Inc.; New York Supreme Court - Nicholas Foscannis v. Edward Corsi, Industrial Commissioner re Claim for Benefits; US Court of Appeals: Bonita, Inc. v. US Department of Labor; correspondence re Pre-Paid Legal Services (The Legal Defender); "The New Republic - Legal Services"; newspaper clippings; "Financial Projections - Group Legal Services" by Bruce Kirschenbaum; Group Legal Services - A Proposal by Bruce Kirschenbaum; "Access of Union Organizers to "Private" Property" - remarks of Max Zimny; routine
  - Legal Services. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Legislation. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 26)